All pirates searching for the treasure of One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, set sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I'm gonna be the king of the pirates!
Two years have passed since the War of the Best in Marineford. Luffy and his crew reunite to continue on to the New World.
Their first stop is Fishman Island.
The Fishman Pirates, led by Horty Jones and assisted by Vander Decken, plot to overthrow King Neptune.
It's not long before the Straw Hats get pulled into the conflict.
Aided by Neptune, Zoro, Usopp, and Brook attempt to escape the palace.
However, their efforts were quickly thwarted by Horty, whose strength increased dramatically after taking a drug known as the energy steroid.
Meanwhile, Luffy and the others arrive at the sea forest where they meet with Jinbei.
Eleven years ago, Arlong was locked away by the government and even knowing what evils he was capable of, I freed him.
The haunting ties! Nami and the Fishman Pirates!
There must be a key to the void and history here somewhere. I'm sure of it.
To think that the missing piece may have been here for several centuries, I'm touched.
If I keep going, I know I'll find something.
Bingo.
But what about King Neptune?
Don't look back. The King's giving us a chance to make it out of here.
The exit!
We made it outside! Activate the coral!
That didn't go well at all. Few guards escaped.
King Neptune sacrificed himself and we have nothing to show for it. We failed you!
We all quit their whining! We followed his orders plain and simple.
Listen up! This is by no means a retreat.
We'll save the King, take back the Ryugu Palace and eradicate that pirate scum in due time.
But first off, we need to contact Prince Fukuboshi and his brothers.
Find the princess as soon as you can, got it?
After that, we'll start regrouping and make our way back to the palace!
What town's closest to where we are now?
Fishburley Hill, sir.
Look out!
Meanwhile, in the high-class district of Fishburley Hills...
Run away!
Get in the line now!
You'll do it if you know what's good for you.
I don't understand. What do you want from us?
Stomp it.
What? It's a test.
But why?
Do as we say. It won't be long before Horde rules this country, he...
Now, step on the picture.
I can't do that.
Yes, you can.
A candy factory town in the Northeast.
Come on! Put your foot down!
I can't!
Huh?
I won't do it!
I can't tread on her image!
I beg you to understand!
Shut up!
Those who won't follow our orders will be branded as human sympathizers!
Which means, you'll also be your enemy!
In the Southeast, outside the Fishman Culture Hall...
This is a damn outfit!
Boy, calm down!
Huh?
I'll make it easy for you. Step on the picture.
Or get ready to leave the island. It's your choice.
That ain't happening!
Come on, guys!
This guy can't be that tough!
Just step on the picture.
Anyone who doesn't wanna...
Is gonna get sliced up real good.
At the Marine Shopping Mall in the East.
What do you mean, leave the country?
This is our home!
We can't leave! No other place on the sea floor gets light!
Besides, you're Fishman too!
What makes you think humans will accept us?
See...
You already know how easily humans will discriminate against anything that's different from them.
Hey! What in the heck is happening to you, man?
He's being choked!
There's no way that humans and Fishmen will ever coexist peacefully.
Your best bet is to accept the rule of hoarding.
Under his reign, we'll have the power to change history.
At Water Wheel Town in the North.
Johnson!
Hey, I think it's your turn.
It'll be easy.
I can't do it!
You still haven't stepped on it yet?
Then what good are ya?
Hey, aren't you... Fukuboshi?
What is the meaning of this? Explain yourself!
You scum! How dare you!
Forcing people to tread on the image of my late mother!
At Coral Hill, after the departure of Luffy and the others...
It's too late! There's nothing we can do!
You're right. We let Vanderdekan escape.
And before that, we couldn't stop the Straw Hats from kidnapping Princess Shirohoshi!
Didn't the princess say she'd be back home in time for dinner?
Fool! They made her say that so we wouldn't chase after them!
There's a group from the Fishman District that's terrorizing the entire island!
Seriously?
Well, did they say what's happening over there?
This is unbelievable!
They said that mermaids are being reported missing all over!
Princess Shirohoshi...
They wouldn't sell her to the Celestial Dragons, would they?
Hey, awful news!
It looks like another mermaid girl just went missing!
This can't be happening!
Form a search party!
Got another one! Who knew it would be this easy?
Even so, I've just gotta get my hands on that one!
She's the biggest mermaid I've ever seen!
If a human-sized mermaid can net me 70 million, then a mermaid that's ten times that size is bound to bring in an even greater haul!
It's a mermaid motherlode!
Any way you slice it, I'll make a fortune!
For you!
Why, hello!
Let me introduce myself!
They have my father!
Please, Princess, do not worry!
Horty may have seized control of the palace, but King Neptune will not give in so easily!
Your father is tougher than you realize!
Huh? You really think so?
I do! Still, I will help save the king at any cost!
Oh! Well, thank you, Jinbei! I'll be counting on you!
Now, please excuse me! I have a matter to discuss with Luffy and his crew!
Beautiful ladies!
Please, have some tea!
Whatever! Just leave it over there for right now!
Yeah, you've bothered us enough already! We're having a serious talk!
You're so sexy when you're stirred with me, Nami!
Sanji-chan hasn't changed one bit!
Good!
Idiot! That's not for you! Give it back!
All right, Jinbei, let's settle this!
Tell me, what did you mean?
Earlier, you said you set our lungs loose into the East Blue!
You... Jinbei, wait!
It's fine! I heard the same thing!
What?
Yeah.
A while back, when Luffy and I first learned about Jinbei of the Seven Warlords,
Yosaku told us about the bargain that Jinbei struck.
He's a warlord!
Yeah, I was really sure they didn't know what he was going to do.
Okay, let me see.
No, I don't know.
Let me see.
What did you mean?
Tell me, what did you mean?
Earlier, you said you set our lungs loose into the East Blue!
You... Jinbei, wait!
It's fine!
I heard the same thing!
What?
Yeah, a while back, when Luffy and I first learned about Jinbei of the Seven Warlords,
Yosaku told us about the bargain that Jinbei struck.
He's a warlord. In exchange for becoming one of the Seven, Jinbei let a dangerous fish man run wild in the East Blue.
Is that what he told us?
Surprise, surprise. You didn't remember.
Wonder how Yosaku's doing now?
Two years ago, when I read about you associating with Jinbei in the newspaper, I honestly didn't know what to think about it.
I thought Jinbei had been the key figure pulling Arlong's strings and telling him what to do.
So, Jinbei, I'll give you a chance to defend what happened, but choose your words wisely.
After all, our very own navigator here had her entire life ruined thanks to your buddy Arlong.
To put it simply, whatever you did turned her world into a living hell.
Depending on what you have to say, I might not forgive you.
Careful, Hatchin.
Don't move too much. Your wounds could open up again.
But he's right. We caused her so much grief. It's horrible. And all the apologizing in the world won't change a thing.
I'm gonna guide ships around all the oceans of the world. It'll be great. And then, I can make maps of all the far left places I'll go.
This map's the first step to realizing your dream. Is that about right?
Yup.
Nami, Nojiko, none of us are actually related.
But that doesn't mean we're not a family.
To be continued...
Pirates! Pirates are coming! Everybody run!
Everybody run!
Greetings and salutations,
you pathetic little humans!
This village is now mine!
Now wait! Yes! Better yet, I'll take this whole island!
100,000 berries for adults and 50,000 for children.
Those who cannot pay, die!
It's okay. I have to do this for my family.
Even if it costs me my life.
It's true, the three of us may not be related by blood.
But we're still a family.
All I've ever wanted to be to those girls was their mother.
And now, I can be...
Enough chitchat! Now get ready to die!
Nojiko! Nami!
Love you.
What's this?
A map, huh?
No! That's my map! I drew it! You can't have it!
A child drew this.
Give it back! Nami, no!
I'm impressed. Good job.
She could be useful. Bring her with us.
Right!
No! Let go of me! Stop! Somebody please help me!
If humans want to eat, they have to work.
But I'll be a good girl and keep drawing maps.
Gather up 100 million berries, then bring it to me.
Do so and I will let your village go.
In addition to giving you your freedom.
Get that thief! She's got our treasure!
If it's just a kid?
I don't care! Shoot her down!
Crap! Find her!
Right!
70 million. Only 70 million more and we'll be free.
Oh! So you made it back after all.
I guess you had nowhere else to go.
In that case, welcome back, Navigator.
I'm sorry. You had a truly horrific experience.
That's right! And she has you to think!
I did. It was a nightmare.
Nothing will ever make me change the way I feel about our lung.
That said, until two years ago, when we made the trip to Saba Odi,
I had no idea that even the strongest of fishmen were routinely persecuted by humans.
When Kami was kidnapped and we tried to save her, I couldn't believe what I saw.
There was Saba Odi Park, right in front of me. The spitting image of Arlong Park before it was destroyed.
We wanted a place all our own. I'm not saying this to make you forgive any of us, but it's true.
Oh, Nami. Arlong. He really hated humans. Too much.
Yes, we went too far.
But for as long as I can remember, we yearned for the world that the humans lived in, above the sea.
Arlong. Me. All of us.
Arlong. Me. On the sea.
Let's go of Arlong. Me. On the sea.
Let's go.
The sea.
Telegram Panthers.
Call 901 6080克 regime.
drove us to hurt people like you.
Wait, take it easy.
I'll go prep some more medicine.
Please lie down.
I heard my people weren't considered anything more than fish way back when.
Then, 200 years ago,
the Ryugu kingdom became a member country of the world government.
They established friendly relations with humans,
and their king was even allowed to participate in the world's summit.
But, despite that, humans still had hate in their hearts.
The beginning of the Great Pirate Era was probably the worst time in my life.
It was hard to be a fish man.
I vividly remember my fear.
Human pirates running wild on the island.
Anywhere you went seemed dangerous.
So much violence, I'll never forget.
Our only safe place in the world was taken over by humans.
Then came that fateful day.
Whitebeard arrived on the island and saved us.
He made his powerful presence felt,
claiming Fishman Island as his own.
Because of him,
peace returned to our home.
However,
humans continue to be prejudiced towards fish men.
All of you saw it firsthand at the Saba Odi Archipelago.
That's the cruel reality.
Naturally,
once someone attains power,
they tend to be resistant to change.
Even though the government theoretically bridged the gap between fish men and humans,
the worst bigots were the people in control to begin with.
The ones who should be leading by example.
Thus,
the relationship between fish men and humans remained the same.
Thankfully,
two individuals rose up on Fishman Island.
Individuals who would help change the course of our beleaguered history.
The first
was Queen Otohime.
She believed we islanders could live in harmony with humans.
She was Princess Shirohoshi's mother.
Then there was him,
the legendary hero named Fisher Tiger,
who freed countless slaves.
That tiger guy, huh?
I think I've heard the name before.
To set himself apart from the humans,
Tiger broke an unspoken rule,
invading the Holy Land of Marie-Joie by himself
and freeing the slaves within.
He would go on to form the Sun Pirates.
Many of its members were fish men who were formerly slaves of the nobles.
Sun Pirates?
Indeed.
You know them
as Arlong,
Hachi,
and myself.
The three of us were part of the very first crew of the Sun Pirates.
But we were known as Fish Man Pirates,
foes of the world government.
That's all that they saw.
Therefore,
we made it that much more difficult for Queen Otohime.
Bless her heart,
our existence prevented much progress.
Queen Otohime was trying to navigate great hardships and improve our future.
At the same time,
Fisher Tiger threw his future away to save those of his race who were suffering as slaves.
No one can say who was right or wrong.
Nevertheless,
they both fought for a better future for fish men and humans.
Each one is a legend.
And both of their tales end in tragedy.
Queen Otohime tries to lead the Ryugu kingdom into an era of coexistence between humans and fish men.
Meanwhile,
the heroic Fisher Tiger battles humans to free their slaves from captivity.
When the tales of these two historic figures cross,
for better or for worse,
the fate of Fish Man Island will be immeasurably changed.
On the next,
One Piece,
a hero who freed the slaves,
an adventurer tiger.
I'm going to be king of the pirates.